Guide to the Henri R. Ferger papers, 1920-1940.
Ferger, Henri R. papers,
- Series II. Visual Materials
  - Subseries IIe. 16mm Films
    - Our Sun in Action, F-424 (Box 17)
    - Personal, 1941-1945; F-425 (Box 17)
    - Personal, 1937; F-426 (Box 17)
    - Personal, 1934-1948, 1963; F-427 (Box 17)
    - Lahure, F-428 (Box 17)
    - Personal, 41932-1933; F-429 (Box 17)
    - John, 1961; F-430 (Box 17)
    - Primary school Barhpur, F-431 (Box 17)
    - Beyond Bacirinath, 1947; F-432 (Box 18)
    - Punjab, Acra, Fatehpur Sekiri, Etah, F-433 (Box 18)
    - Scout drills, F-434 (Box 18)
    - New York City, F-435 (Box 18)
    - Pindari, 1938; F-436 (Box 18)
    - FC College Lahure, Physical education, games, and drills, F-437 (Box 18)
    - Assam, 1940; F-438 (Box 18)
    - Extras, F-439 (Box 18)
    - India, 1961; F-440 (Box 18)
    - Agra to Kalim Pong, F-441 (Box 18)
    - Film 12, F-442 (Box 18)
    - Personal, 1949; F-443 (Box 18)
    - Personal, 1948-1949; F-444 (Box 18)
    - Inside India, F-445 (Box 18)
    - Kalim Pong, F-446 (Box 18)
    - India cuts, F-447 (Box 18)
    - Etawah Story, F-448 (Box 18)
    - Transport and Village Life, F-449 (Box 18)
    - This is my Father's World, F-450 (Box 19)
    - Tree of Wealth, F-451 (Box 19)
    - Music of India, F-452 (Box 19)
    - Inside India, F-453 (Box 19)
    - Baharat Natyam, F-454 (Box 19)
    - Indian Scouts, F-455 (Box 19)
    - Yatra, 1947; F-456 (Box 19)
    - Good Samaritan, silent, F-457 (Box 19)
    - "For Jeanette Moore", F-458 (Box 19)
    - John 2, F-459 (Box 19)
    - HR Ferger at Cody Wyo, 1949; F-460 (Box 19)
    - Pindari, 1939; F-461 (Box 19)
    - Good Samaritan, F-462 (Box 19)
    - Sounds of India, 1959; F-463 (Box 19)
    - Naga Hills, F-464 (Box 19)
    - Assam, 1948; F-465 (Box 19)
    - Naga Hills, 2 and 3, F-466 (Box 19)
    - Historic India, F-467 (Box 19)
    - Holy Himalayas, F-468 (Box 19)
    - Famous Places of India, F-469 (Box 19)
    - Revenge on the Range, F-470 (Box 19)
    - Film 13, F-471 (Box 28)